sidecubes.com 2014-12-10

# SideCubes - Privacy

We at Veristaff.com inc. and its wholly owned subsidiaries ("Veristaff.com") are committed to providing web sites and software products that respect the privacy of its visitors and users respectively. This page summarizes the privacy policy and practices for all Veristaff.com Web Sites, as well as for the Veristaff.com software products. 

The Veristaff.com privacy policy is designed to allow the users of its web sites and software applications (the "Veristaff.com Products") with information allowing them to make informed choices with respect to their use of the Veristaff.com Products and their provision of personal information. 

Your use of Veristaff.com, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as the Terms of Use of particular Veristaff.com Products and all of its dispute resolution provisions including arbitration, limitation on damages and choice of law. Veristaff.com reserves the right to change our Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use at any time. Non-material changes and clarifications will take effect immediately, and material changes will take effect within 30 days of their posting on this site. We encourage you to regularly review the Veristaff.com Product web sites to familiarize yourself with changes which may occur from time-to-time. If we make changes, we will post them and will indicate at the top of this page the policy's new effective date. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or through notice on our home page. We encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you, your account and information we obtain by your use of Veristaff.com Products or services. 

When you use the Veristaff.com Products, you will be providing two types of information: information you explicitly provide through interaction with the Veristaff.com Product, and information which is obtained by virtue of your visiting the Veristaff.com web sites 

###  **Information Collected**

###  Personal Information 

Currently, we do not ask you to register for our products because we simply do not need you to. We do not require the submission of any information that identifies you personally, such as your name, address and other ("Personal Information"). However, when you commence direct communications with us, we may retain such communications and the accompanying Personal Information in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. 

Statistical Information we collect and aggregate non-identifying information regarding users use of our Products, including, inter alia, advertisements viewed, pages browsed, search inquiries, offers and services that interest you, the type of browser you are using, your IP address, the URL you have come from and the time spent at that URL, cookies and your domain type and server ("Statistical Information"). 

###  Browsing History and IP 

In order to facilitate, improve, refine, personalize and match the identification and presentation of our products and SimilarSites.com results to your browsing preferences and habits, we collect information regarding your use of our Product including URL and Statistical Information of websites you may be browsing while Product is installed ("Browsing History"), and together with the Statistical Information "Non-Personal Information"). 

While we would never collect any Personal Information submitted to such websites, note that Browsing History is aggregated separately for each specific IP, in order to continuously improve our products and provide the most relevant SimilarSites results for each different location to better understand Internet trends statistics. While we would never collect any Personal Information submitted to such websites, note that Browsing History is aggregated separately for each specific IP, in order to continuously improve our products and provide the most relevant SimilarSites results for each different location to better understand Internet trends statistics. 

That said, IP addresses, while identifying a device connected to the Internet, and its general location, are in themselves anonymous and contain no information regarding the identity of the ultimate person using the device – such identity is known solely to your ISP. 

Moreover, IP addresses assigned by ISPs are generally dynamic and subject to frequent change – static IP addresses are generally assigned only at subscriber's specific request and frequently require an additional fee. 

###  Information obtained by virtue of your visiting   
Veristaff.com web sites 

When you use Veristaff.com Products, we will collect the following information:  
1\. The Internet domain and IP address from which you access the Veristaff.com Products;  
2\. Screen resolution of your monitor;  
3\. The date and time you access the Veristaff.com Products;  
4\. The page you are visiting with the Veristaff.com Products  
5\. If you linked to a Veristaff.com website from another referring website, the address of that website.  

By using the Veristaff.com Products, you are consenting to have your personal data transferred to and processed both within and without the United States of America  

By using the Veristaff.com website, you agree to the preceding uses of your information in this way by Veristaff.com.
